[{"answer": "You -- the first thing that happened is he came in through the exit door, through, you know, what is being said is tear gas.", "docId": "120720pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "What was the first that you knew that this was going down?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "So this has been a long day and I appreciate how long a day it's been for all of you in the media.", "docId": "120720pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Governor Hickenlooper?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "If we have information about a motive, we will not share it with you.", "docId": "120720pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "Has he said anything about why he did this?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "I won't talk about his admissions.", "docId": "120720pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "He's talking to you though?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "My understanding is all the weapons he possessed, he possessed legally.", "docId": "120720pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "(INAUDIBLE) that perfectly legal?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "It was a gas mask.", "docId": "120720pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "What about the mask?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "Well, at the -- I did.", "docId": "120720pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "Did you realize at the time you've been hit by a bullet?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "No, I was in the middle -- I ended up on the row over, and then I ended up crawling out.", "docId": "120720pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Could you see him?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "It's -- it's not right.", "docId": "120720pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "What is your reaction to the fact that this young man was legally able in the last two months to obtain four weapons, including an assault rifle, and so much ammunition and commit this atrocity?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "No, this -- my thought was this is how it ends.", "docId": "120720pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Jamie, did you think that you were going to get out alive or did you fear that everyone was going to die in there?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "He's a quiet guy, you know, very nice.", "docId": "120720pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "What kind of boy was he?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "No, I haven't been able to talk to her because too many people tried to get her.", "docId": "120720pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Have you been able to speak to her today?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "First of all, I want to express my grief and my deep condolences for the victims.", "docId": "120720pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "And would stricter gun control have made a difference in this case?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Honestly, Piers, I think this is the wrong night to be doing this.", "docId": "120720pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Piers, I think, like you said, that legitimate cause existed yesterday.", "docId": "120720pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "Given what has happened today, do you think there is now legitimate cause to press politicians for tougher gun control in America?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "The American people need to express their outrage directly to their representatives on every single level.", "docId": "120720pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "That can't be right, can it?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "Well, it did bring back some terrible memories.", "docId": "120720pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "What was your reaction to what happened?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "Well, I think any decision of serious political issues or policy issues are not going to be had now.", "docId": "120720pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "Do you think that Washington is going to wake up tomorrow, perhaps, and realize that America simply can't keep having this number of outrages involving guns?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "First of all, thanks a lot.", "docId": "120720pmt", "aSentId": 656, "question": "What are your feelings about what's happened here today?", "qSentId": 655}]